<resources>
    <string name="app_name">M.V DIABEAT</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="details">The appointments team will check the availability of the consultant and date
        requested and send you a confirmation mail or call you on the mobile no. shared by you.</string>
    <string name="aboutUsDetails">
        M.V. Hospital for Diabetes situated at Royapuram, Chennai,  was established by late Prof. M. Viswanathan, Doyen of Diabetology in India in 1954 as a general hospital. In 1971 it became a hospital exclusively for diabetes care. Under Prof. M. Viswanathans professional and administrative leadership, the hospital has grown to achieve the status of a teaching institution of international excellence. It has, at present, 100 beds for the treatment of diabetes and its complications. Over the years it has grown to be one of the largest referral centres for Diabetes, with more than 3,00,000 patients registered to-date. It is recognised as an internationally known tertiary care centre for referral of Diabetic patients requiring super-specialist is opinion and management.We are committed to being an accredited leader of quality health care with a commitment to continuous quality improvement, setting new standards, providing curative, preventive, and evidence based medicine in an ethically based cost-effective environment using state-of-the-art technology. We strive to excel in anticipating and meeting our communities needs, wants, and expectations in an environment conducive to teamwork.

    </string>

    <string name="about_us_points">- Back in 1954, our late visionary leader Prof. M. Viswanathan started the M.V. Hospital for Diabetes, which at the time in question, was the first-of-its-kind. \n \n

- He was criticised for having turned his focus to diabetes during a time where infectious diseases were prevalent.   \n\n


- Forward to 2019 the statistics show that, 450 million of the world’s populations are currently diabetic, with India sitting not so pretty at the top as the capital of world diabetes.   \n\n



- Over the last 65 years, M.V. Hospital has flourished by being an internationally accredited leader in providing quality diabetes healthcare.  \n\n



- The quality of treatment and products sold by the Hospital is backed by years of research by Prof.M. Viswanathan Research Centre, which started back in 1973.   \n\n



-It is accredited to Tamil Nadu Dr. M.G.R Medical University and is also now a temple of learning for aspiring diabetologists across the country.   \n\n



-The hospital remains to be the only one of 5 centres in the world to be designated as a WHO Collaborating Centre for Diabetes.  \n\n</string>
    <string name="txt_nike_shoes">Nike Power-Run</string>
    <string name="txt_buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="Rupees">₹</string>
    <string name="nike_power_run">Nike Power-Run</string>
    <string name="txt_product_price">1</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="action_next">Next</string>
    <string name="action_demo">Demo</string>
    <string name="title_activity_base">BaseActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_net_banking">NetBankingActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cash_card">CashCardActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_emi">EmiActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_card">CardActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_cards">UserCardsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_payments">PaymentsActivity</string>
    <string name="pay_now">Pay</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="click_here">Click here</string>
    <string name="if_cvv_and_expiry_on_card"> &#160;if you have CVV and Expiry on your card</string>
    <string name="if_dont_cvv_and_expiry_on_card"> &#160;if you don\'t have CVV and Expiry on your card</string>
    <string name="net_banking">Net Banking</string>
    <string name="title_activity_merchant_payment">MerchantPaymentActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_verify_api">VerifyApiActivity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->


    <string name="test">Test</string>
    <string name="production">Production</string>

    <string-array name="environment_array">
        <item>@string/test</item>
        <item>@string/production</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="use_live_key_in_production_environment">Please use your live merchant key in production environment</string>
    <string name="could_not_receive_data">Could not receive data</string>
    <string name="appintment_message">Thanks for the appointment booking request. \n Our appointments booking team will check the availability of the consultant and date requested and send you a confirmation mail or call you on the mobile no. shared by u</string>
<!--    <string name="warning">M.V. Diabeat is live! \nPlease note that appointments can be scheduled only after May 3rd, 2020. Shopping services and delivery as well will not be available until the countrywide lockdown has been lifted. Thank you for your cooperation.</string>-->

    <string name="warning">Please note that delivery may be affected due to lockdown.</string>


</resources>
